let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which player has the most Premier League appearances?",
        answer: "C. Gareth Barry",
        options: [
            "A. Frank Lampard",
            "B. John Terry",
            "C. Gareth Barry",
            "D. Ryan Giggs"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which player has scored the most Premier League goals?",
        answer: "A. Alan Shearer",
        options: [
            "A. Alan Shearer",
            "B. Andy Cole",
            "C. Thierry Henry",
            "D. Wayne Rooney"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which player has the most Premier League assists?",
        answer: "D. Ryan Giggs",
        options: [
            "A. Kevin De Bruyne",
            "B. Cesc Fábregas",
            "C. Frank Lampard",
            "D. Ryan Giggs"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which team has won the most Premier League titles?",
        answer: "B. Manchester United",
        options: [
            "A. Liverpool",
            "B. Manchester United",
            "C. Chelsea",
            "D. Arsenal"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which player has scored the most Premier League hat-tricks?",
        answer: "D. Sergio Agüero",
        options: [
            "A. Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "B. Wayne Rooney",
            "C. Luis Suárez",
            "D. Sergio Agüero"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which team has won Premier League title with the most points?",
        answer: "A. Manchester City",
        options: [
            "A. Manchester City",
            "B. Liverpool",
            "C. Nottingham Forest",
            "D. Manchester United"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which team has got the most defeats in total?",
        answer: "C. Everton",
        options: [
            "A. Aston Villa",
            "B. Sunderland",
            "C. Everton",
            "D. Southampton"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which player has scored the most Premier League goals at one club?",
        answer: "B. Harry Kane",
        options: [
            "A. Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "B. Harry Kane",
            "C. Luis Suárez",
            "D. Thierry Henry"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which player has made the most Premier League appearances as a substitute?",
        answer: "A. James Milner",
        options: [
            "A. James Milner",
            "B. Marcus Bent",
            "C. Brad Friedel",
            "D. Ryan Giggs"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which goalkeeper has got the most clean sheets in Premier League?",
        answer: "A. Petr Čech",
        options: [
            "A. Petr Čech",
            "B. David James",
            "C. Pepe Reina",
            "D. David de Gea"
        ]
    }
];
